[PARKING] I spoiled you previously.
[موقف السيارات] لقد دللتك سابقاً.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
I will be the one
سأكون أنا الشخص
taking charge in our relationship.
تولي زمام الأمور في علاقتنا.
It hurts.
إنه مؤلم.
Endure it.
تحمّل ذلك.
But it looks like your shoulder is hurting.
لكن يبدو أن كتفك يؤلمك.
You fooled me,
لقد خدعتني،
and now you care?
والآن تهتم؟
Do you think I'll believe it?
هل تعتقد أنني سأصدق ذلك؟
I did abandon you just now
لقد تخليت عنك للتو
but it's also true that I care about you now.
لكن من الصحيح أيضاً أنني أهتم لأمرك الآن.
It just looks like you
يشبهك تماماً
injected the inhibitor violently.
قام بحقن المثبط بعنف.
No matter how much you hate me and want me dead,
مهما بلغت كراهيتك لي ورغبتك في موتي،
there's no need to harm yourself.
لا داعي لإيذاء نفسك.
You'll be the only one getting hurt...
ستكون أنت الوحيد الذي سيتأذى...
Then, don't run away next time.
إذن، لا تهرب في المرة القادمة.
I can't do it.
لا أستطيع فعل ذلك.
Forming a pact
إبرام اتفاق
can only be done with two people who like each other.
لا يمكن القيام بذلك إلا مع شخصين يحبان بعضهما البعض.
So,
لذا،
I must work harder
يجب أن أعمل بجد أكبر
to make you fall for me.
لأجعلك تقعين في حبي.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
This is not about working harder or not.
الأمر لا يتعلق بالعمل بجدية أكبر أو عدمه.
What you're feeling
ما تشعر به
is purely a Ren's desire to possess an Yin.
إنها مجرد رغبة رين في امتلاك يين.
You're emotionally detached.
أنت منفصل عاطفياً.
You might not fall in love with anyone in your life.
قد لا تقع في حب أي شخص في حياتك.
Might not?
ربما لا؟
That means
هذا يعني
I might.
ربما.
No.
لا.
I don't want to gamble.
لا أريد أن أقامر.
When you went berserk, even your parents were...
عندما فقدت أعصابك، حتى والداك...
I did not.
لم أفعل.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
Anyway,
على أي حال،
personally, liking someone
شخصياً، الإعجاب بشخص ما
is showing respect and understanding.
إظهار الاحترام والتفهم.
It is
إنها
a healthy relationship where you can
علاقة صحية حيث يمكنك
hand over
تسليم
your most cherished thing to the other person.
أغلى ما تملكه بالنسبة للشخص الآخر.
A relationship
علاقة
that you might never understand.
قد لا تفهم ذلك أبداً.
You really don't know how to choose your timing.
أنت حقاً لا تعرف كيف تختار التوقيت المناسب.
I'm dying.
أنا أموت.
I'm not in the mood to be a third wheel.
لستُ في مزاج يسمح لي بأن أكون طرفاً ثالثاً.
Give me your blood.
أعطني دمك.
Why do you want my blood?
لماذا تريد دمي؟
You haven't formed a pact with each other, right?
لم تعقدا اتفاقاً مع بعضكما البعض، أليس كذلك؟
Then, your blood can still save me.
إذن، لا يزال بإمكان دمك أن ينقذني.
Hurry.
عجل.
Otherwise, I'll rip both of you apart
وإلا، فسأمزقكما إرباً إرباً
when I go completely berserk later.
عندما أفقد صوابي تماماً لاحقاً.
How scary.
يا له من أمر مرعب.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
We should escape now.
يجب أن نهرب الآن.
The people of the Special Administration Bureau
موظفو مكتب الإدارة الخاصة
treated me as a weapon in the beginning.
لقد عاملوني كسلاح في البداية.
Later, they sent me here to become a lab rat
فيما بعد، أرسلوني إلى هنا لأصبح فأر تجارب
when they felt I was about to outlive my usefulness.
عندما شعروا أنني على وشك أن أفقد فائدتي.
The experimental equipment caused me so much pain every day.
لقد تسببت لي المعدات التجريبية بألم شديد كل يوم.
I'm scared of that feeling.
أنا خائف من ذلك الشعور.
He passed out.
فقد وعيه.
Resuscitate him immediately.
قم بإنعاشه فوراً.
It's too late.
لقد فات الأوان.
If kept alive,
إذا تم الحفاظ عليه على قيد الحياة،
these people will become scums who endanger our society.
سيصبح هؤلاء الأشخاص حثالة تُهدد مجتمعنا.
They should feel honored to be able to contribute
ينبغي أن يشعروا بالفخر لقدرتهم على المساهمة.
to the scientific development of inhibitors.
للتطوير العلمي للمثبطات.
Let's continue the experiment.
لنواصل التجربة.
No!
لا!
I beg you!
أرجوك!
Please let go of me!
أرجوك اتركني!
I don't want to die!
لا أريد أن أموت!
I just don't want to die.
أنا فقط لا أريد أن أموت.
Don't abandon me here.
لا تتركني هنا.
Your words are useless.
كلامك لا فائدة منه.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Save me.
أنقذني.
Give me your blood.
أعطني دمك.
Are you all right?
هل أنت بخير؟
You are so annoying!
أنت مزعج للغاية!
You ruin my plan all the time.
أنت تفسد خطتي طوال الوقت.
So it was
وهكذا كان
all an act?
كل هذا تمثيل؟
As expected, it's no use
وكما هو متوقع، لا فائدة منه
pleading to an Yin like you.
أتوسل إلى يين مثلك.
Gu,
ل،
what are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Listen.
يستمع.
All the Yin are bad.
جميع عناصر الين سيئة.
They are just like those in Administration Bureau uniforms.
إنهم يشبهون تماماً أولئك الذين يرتدون زيّ المكتب الإداري.
They treat you like an animal!
إنهم يعاملونك كالحيوان!
People from the Special Administration Bureau will arrive soon.
سيصل أفراد من مكتب الإدارة الخاصة قريباً.
Try saying the same thing
حاول أن تقول الشيء نفسه
to them.
لهم.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
You're despicable.
أنت حقير.
I won't let them torture me to death.
لن أدعهم يعذبونني حتى الموت.
I'll also make them feel pain.
سأجعلهم يشعرون بالألم أيضاً.
I obtained something good.
لقد حصلت على شيء جيد.
It will significantly weaken
سيؤدي ذلك إلى إضعافه بشكل كبير
our vitals
مؤشراتنا الحيوية
for a certain period.
لفترة معينة.
Those foolish researchers
هؤلاء الباحثون الحمقى
will surely assume
سيفترض بالتأكيد
we died from taking
متنا بسبب تناولنا
their new inhibitors.
مثبطاتهم الجديدة.
The truth is,
الحقيقة هي،
we are fine.
نحن بخير.
When we wake up,
عندما نستيقظ،
I'm going to kill all of them.
سأقتلهم جميعاً.
I want to eat a candy.
أريد أن آكل قطعة حلوى.
You'll get a toothache.
ستصاب بألم في الأسنان.
Eating it makes me happier.
تناوله يجعلني أكثر سعادة.
I want it.
أريدها.
In the future,
في المستقبل،
this place will only be full of
هذا المكان سيكون مليئًا فقط بـ
free, happy, and united
أحرار، سعداء، ومتحدون
Ren and Yin.
رين ويين.
[Security]
[حماية]
Did you regret treating me like that just now?
هل ندمت على معاملتك لي بهذه الطريقة قبل قليل؟
I can't empathize with you.
لا أستطيع أن أتعاطف معك.
If you just wanted to escape alive,
إذا كنت ترغب فقط في النجاة،
why killed so many people?
لماذا قتل كل هؤلاء الناس؟
Everyone feels pain,
الجميع يشعر بالألم،
not just you.
ليس أنت فقط.
Also, not everyone
أيضًا، ليس الجميع
will turn a blind eye
سوف يتغاضى عن الأمر
to the pain you feel.
إلى الألم الذي تشعر به.
Good job.
أحسنت.
Troublesome society scums like him
أمثال هؤلاء الحثالة الاجتماعية المزعجة
should be eliminated.
يجب التخلص منه.
All right.
حسنًا.
Let's split up and find Nongyu.
لننفصل ونبحث عن نونغيو.
You seem very disappointed. What's wrong?
يبدو عليك خيبة الأمل الشديدة. ما الأمر؟
I'm wondering
أتساءل
if you're plotting something evil again.
إذا كنت تخطط لشيء شرير مرة أخرى.
Yes.
نعم.
I am.
أنا أكون.
I'm racking my brain
أحاول جاهدًا أن أفهم
to find a way
لإيجاد طريقة
to slowly
ببطء
and
و
gradually
تدريجياً
tame
ترويض
a disobedient prey
فريسة عاصية
before eating it.
قبل تناوله.
I'll think about
سأفكر في الأمر
what you told me just now.
ما أخبرتني به للتو.
Nongyu!
نونجيو!
(Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
I...
أنا...
Nongyu!
نونجيو!
That's my brother.
هذا أخي.
Remember.
يتذكر.
Hide the existence of Xie Xinxu.
إخفاء وجود Xie Xinxu.
After all, I get agitated easily by the people
في النهاية، أنا أنزعج بسهولة من الناس
of the Special Administration Bureau.
مكتب الإدارة الخاصة.
If I go berserk and hurt them,
إذا فقدت أعصابي وألحقت بهم الأذى،
that'll be your fault.
سيكون ذلك خطأك.
I...
أنا...
You are free.
أنت حر.
Did I really just get rid of him like that?
هل تخلصت منه بهذه الطريقة حقاً؟
Siyuan.
سيوان.
Where were you just now?
أين كنت قبل قليل؟
Don't bark at me.
لا تنبح عليّ.
I've been
لقد كنت
running all night to flee from a bunch of lunatics.
الركض طوال الليل هرباً من مجموعة من المجانين.
[Affinity]
[التقارب]
So, did Mr. Ding
وكذلك فعل السيد دينغ
tell you everything about Ren and Yin?
هل يمكنني إخبارك بكل شيء عن رين ويين؟
As well as Nan Xing?
وكذلك نان شينغ؟
Stop.
قف.
Can you let me get some sleep before we discuss this?
هل يمكنك أن تدعني أنام قليلاً قبل أن نناقش هذا الأمر؟
That was scary.
كان ذلك مخيفاً.
Didn't you say you'd spare me?
ألم تقل إنك ستعفو عني؟
I'm taking it back now.
سأتراجع عن كلامي الآن.
You can't escape from me.
لن تستطيع الهروب مني.
So he didn't appear in my nightmare,
إذن لم يظهر في كابوسي،
but rather in a wet...
بل بالأحرى في جو رطب...
Are we having soup today?
هل سنتناول الحساء اليوم؟
Even the thunder couldn't wake you up,
حتى الرعد لم يستطع إيقاظك،
yet you smelled soup and woke up on your own.
لكنك شممت رائحة الحساء واستيقظت بمفردك.
Another day of living happily
يوم آخر من العيش بسعادة
and waking up to good food.
والاستيقاظ على طعام جيد.
Siyuan.
سيوان.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Compared to the Ren,
بالمقارنة مع عصر النهضة،
we are considered fortunate
نحن نعتبر محظوظين
to be Yin.
أن يكون يين.
We don't lose our freedom.
لن نفقد حريتنا.
We won't be treated as living weapons
لن يتم التعامل معنا كأسلحة حية
or become test subjects.
أو يصبحون موضوعات تجارب.
Who told you that?
من أخبرك بذلك؟
You are shocked too, right?
أنت مصدوم أيضاً، أليس كذلك؟
The superiors of the Special Administration Bureau did this in secret.
قام رؤساء مكتب الإدارة الخاصة بذلك سراً.
Of course, they are hiding it from everyone else.
بالطبع، إنهم يخفون ذلك عن الجميع.
I heard it from a Ren.
سمعت ذلك من رين.
Not everything he said
ليس كل ما قاله
is true.
هذا صحيح.
The higher-ups
كبار المسؤولين
will have a thorough investigation regarding Genus.
سيتم إجراء تحقيق شامل بشأن الجنس.
Oh,
أوه،
do you dream about Xie Xinxu a lot?
هل تحلم كثيراً بـ Xie Xinxu؟
Your burning question burns just like your soup.
سؤالك الملحّ يحرقك تماماً كما يحرق حسائك.
Do you always dream of him
هل تحلمين به دائماً؟
because you find him scary subconsciously?
لأنك تجده مخيفاً دون وعي؟
If I tell you
إذا أخبرتك
that there's a high chance that he didn't kill his parents,
أن هناك احتمالاً كبيراً بأنه لم يقتل والديه،
will it reduce your fear a little?
هل سيخفف ذلك من خوفك قليلاً؟
The police did not find evidence of his murder back then.
لم تعثر الشرطة على أي دليل على مقتله آنذاك.
Later, he died from an illness.
وفي وقت لاحق، توفي بسبب مرض.
No new clues were discovered
لم يتم اكتشاف أي أدلة جديدة
so the case was closed.
وهكذا أُغلقت القضية.
Does it mean
هل يعني ذلك
he is not dangerous to society?
ألا يشكل خطراً على المجتمع؟
Keeping his existence a secret should be...
ينبغي أن يكون إبقاء وجوده سراً...
I also have a better way
لديّ أيضاً طريقة أفضل
of removing your fear.
إزالة خوفك.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Marriage.
زواج.
Then, you won't have time to think about another man.
عندها، لن يكون لديكِ وقت للتفكير في رجل آخر.
Wu Siyuan!
وو سيوان!
Are you a devil?
هل أنت شيطان؟
♪A ray of morning sun shines through the cafe curtains♪
♪تتسلل أشعة شمس الصباح عبر ستائر المقهى♪
♪Your fingertips touch the fantasy on the rim of the cup♪
♪تلامس أطراف أصابعك الخيال على حافة الكأس♪
♪The swaying windchime knocks away the time difference♪
♪أجراس الرياح المتأرجحة تزيل فارق التوقيت♪
♪The unread poem waits for a reply♪
♪ القصيدة غير المقروءة تنتظر ردًا ♪
[Saige Stadium]
[ملعب سايج]
Isn't this the stadium?
أليس هذا هو الملعب؟
There's an official blind dating event here tomorrow.
هناك فعالية رسمية للتعارف بين أشخاص لا يعرفون بعضهم غداً.
It's specifically for Yin and Ren.
إنه مخصص تحديداً لـ Yin و Ren.
Mr. Ding probably told you about the pact, right?
ربما أخبرك السيد دينغ عن الاتفاق، أليس كذلك؟
The government
الحكومة
is very supportive of this endeavor.
وهو يدعم هذا المسعى بشدة.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
I'm a little confused now.
أشعر ببعض الحيرة الآن.
You mean
تقصد
you also arranged a Ren
لقد رتبت أيضًا رين
as my blind date previously?
كما حدث في موعدي الغرامي السابق؟
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Why?
لماذا؟
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪